Gavin Max M

Tiruchchirappalli, Tamil Nadu 620019 gavinmaxmwn7cn_zmd@indeedemail.com +9163817 49226

Recruiter with extensive experience in HR domains such as global recruitment and retention, strategic planning, talent development, and performance management. Over a year of outstanding performance in full cycle hiring across numerous sectors and functions.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Talent Acquisition Associate

CHASE HR Consulting - Chennai, Tamil Nadu November 2022 to January 2024

- Hands-on Experience in full-cycle recruitment from strategic sourcing, screening of candidates, presentation of candidate.
- Worked for Full-time or Permanent, Contract to hire and Contract positions.
- Recruitments utilizing various sourcing method like Web portals (i.e., Naukri, Shine)
- Screening, short-listing candidates profile as per the requirements of Business.
- Coordinating with candidates for interview & conducting telephonic interview before short listing candidates.
- Scheduling & coordinating the interview between Candidate & Panels.
- Maintaining daily/ weekly/monthly reports such as interview status reports, closure reports & feedback reports.
- TECHNOLOGIES: Cloud technologies like AWS, Azure, Quality Assurance like Automation testing, Manual testing, API testing, Selenium, etc., Front/back-end technologies like CSS, JavaScript, Angular JS, Node JS, React JS, etc., Databases like Oracle, DB2, MySQL.

Junior Executive

Straive - Tiruchchirappalli, Tamil Nadu February 2020 to September 2022

- Planning & leading administration of Management Information System (MIS) for achieving threshold level performance
- Producing tables, pivot reports and charts for use in key decision making processes.
- Generating reports every month covering I/O, billing, issues & dispatched data.
- Tracking TAT metrics daily & organized for reporting purposes
- Tracking departmental expenditures, project schedules, team performance & progress.
- Determined readiness of written pieces, made changes & approved final versions for publication.
- Collaborated with writers & graphic designers to develop content schedules & plan workflows.
- Communicated with writers to collaboratively assess work & guide editorial improvements.

Education

Bachelor's degree in Electronics Engineering

Mookambigai College of Engineering - Pudukkottai, Tamil Nadu June 2015 to April 2019

Skills / IT Skills

- Human resources
- Recruiting
- Communication skills
- HR sourcing
- Human resources management
- Talent acquisition
- Training & development
- Microsoft Office
- Workforce management